webanonymizer.org 2008-11-23

# ProxyPedia.org Online free resource for finding fast and secure proxys

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our web sites. We do not sell or lend out your email address or any other personal information. Your information is kept private and only seen by our authorized support staff.

## General

ProxyPedia.org, TradiArt& Co., and its affiliates are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using proxypedia.org. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit proxypedia.org.

## Information We Collect

### General

When you register, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, age, address, e-mail address, credit-card number and facts about your computers and similar information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

### Surveys

We may conduct occasional online surveys. For example, when you're within our Web site, you may see a pop-up window offering you the optional opportunity of participating in a survey. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate.

### Web Site Usage Information

We automatically log IP addresses and Web site usage statistics when you visit our Web site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our Web site, including the number and frequency of visitors and the length of their visits.

### How We Use Information Collected

We may use information in the following ways: For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information including, for example, to enable us to process, validate and verify orders. To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services. To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences. Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of TradiArt & Co. We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Subscriber Agreement or Terms of Use (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so.

### Cookies

We do not employ any cookie technology on our Web site for the gathering of information or statistics. The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. Cookies are used on our secure server(s) for the purpose of tracking orders. Resellers of our products and services may decide to put a link on their web page to our secure cookie. This cookie only contains the reseller ID. No other information about you or your system is contained within the cookie.

### Proxy Services

Proxy connection logs are kept that enable our management team to monitor bandwidth usage and the number of page views. This information is only used by our staff so that we can continue to provide top quality service. Without knowing which proxy machines have high serverloads, or which network segments are being consumed, we would not be able to add a server or allocate more bandwidth where it is needed. These logs are kept and compiled into a database program that enable our staff to compare connections and bandwidth against past months. This and all other information gathered by our servers, is kept private and is not released to the public or sold to any third party.

### SPAM

TradiArt & Co. offers services such as virtual hosting, proxy, co-location, etc. You cannot use these or other LockDown services for any kind of illegal activity or SPAM. Our penalty for spam abuse is $25.00 per message and your account will be terminated. Note: In addition, some states have anti spam laws that allow the person receiving the message to sue the owner of the equipment for up to $500.00 per message. In these cases TradiArt & Co. will turn over your personal information on request. i.e. If it was found that a bulk mailing was sent out from you and your account with us was terminated for this reason, your information would be provided to the person or organization requesting it from any state with an anti spam law. Policy Modifications We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.

### Transfer to Spain

If you are located outside Spain, please note that the information you provide to us will be transferred to this country.

### Comments and Questions

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us at contact (@) proxypedia.org
